[
  {
    "front": "penser",
    "back": "思"
  },
  {
    "front": "commencer",
    "back": "始"
  },
  {
    "front": "fabriquer, faire",
    "back": "作"
  },
  {
    "front": "motif, lettre, phrase, littérature",
    "back": "文"
  },
  {
    "front": "lettre, caractère, écriture",
    "back": "字"
  },
  {
    "front": "proche, près",
    "back": "近"
  },
  {
    "front": "maison, famille",
    "back": "家"
  },
  {
    "front": "construire, être construit",
    "back": "建"
  },
  {
    "front": "habiter",
    "back": "住"
  },
  {
    "front": "endroit, lieu",
    "back": "所"
  }
]
